Pray Somaldo

Email: praysomaldo@ymail.com Mobile: 081317195001

ABOUT ME

First of all, I like build something related to AI products. I have build computer vision products that have deployed in some retail area with python integrated to MySQL as databases using TensorRT to deploy. I also aiming to research on computer vision by following the updates on that area. On the other hand, I develop my skill by continously learn by taking training from Kominfo and bootcamp such as Bangkit. I realized that I love learning even when I have to repeat it from zero. Thus, I always practicing my skills and like to learn something new.

EDUCATION

• Universitas Indonesia

Master of Computer Science

Depok 2019 – 2020

• Universitas Indonesia

 $Bachelor\ of\ Mathematics$

Depok Sept. 2013 – Aug. 2017

EXPERIENCE

• Sugihart Digital Imaji

Machine Learning Engineer

Grand Galaxy, Bekasi

August 2019 - Present

- **People Counting Project**: Build computer vision models to detect person for retail industry or department store to generate visitor data and gain insight for advertising their products also classify person data into male and female for specific advertisement.
- Face recognition attendance system: Build face recognition for company attendance system with real time speed to monitoring employees and integrated it with Odoo as ERP

Technology used: python, Tensorflow, Darkflow, Yolo, TensorRT, jupyter notebook, MySQL

• Kurio

Data Science Engineer

Slipi, Jakarta

Sept 2018 - Feb 2019

- Sensitive Classifier: Build and test machine learning model to filter inappropriate articles start from gathering article data, labelling, pre-processing, training, testing, until make an endpoint to deploy the classifier as a service.
- Category Classifier: Build machine learning model similar to sensitive classifier, but with various category such as tech, sport, politics, gadget, e-sport, etc and validate the model to achieve up to 95% accuracy.

Technology used: python, pipenv, pyenv, mongoDB, jupyter notebook, docker, google cloud platform, flask, spacy, github, jira

• Metra Digital Media

Junior Data Scientist

Pancoran, Jakarta

Oct 2017 - Jan 2018

- Web Crawling: Web Crawling and update data then load it to server data using python
- Clustering: Clustering and analyze data for campaign needs and visualize it based on region by density, salary, religion, etc.
- Data Gathering: Data management and querying using SQL for report needs Technology used: SPSS, R, MySQL, jupyter notebook, zeppelin, hadoop

SKILLS

- Python: beautifulsoup, featuretools, flask, joblib, matplotlib, numpy, pandas, seaborn, scikit-learn, scipy, spacy, unittest, plotly, pyspark, request, opency, PIL, imutils
- R: caret, dplyr,ggplot
- Matlab: image processing
- SQL: MySQL, Postgre, NoSQL

Publications

• Paper Detection of Diabetic Retinopathy on Retinal Images using Naive Bayes	Symomath, Bandung 2017
CERTIFICATE	
• Artificial Intelligence Digitalent Scholarship in Artificial Intelligence, Fakultas Teknik UI, Depok	Kominfo, Depok 2019
• Introduction to TensorFlow for Artificial Intelligence Course from deeplearning.ai with coursera	Deeplearning.ai 2020